<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DroneLog</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="news_a">President Joe Biden has laid out plans to vaccinate 70% of US adults by 4 July and roll out the shots for 12- to 15-year-olds as soon as possible. Mr Bidens new goal includes having 160 million adults fully vaccinated by Independence Day. The target is well within reach as 105 million have already had the required jabs, and the US is vaccinating nearly a million adults per day. But the vaccination rate is half of what it was just three weeks ago. Mr Biden said his administration was working to win over "doubters" about the shots. Israel - a world leader in vaccination rates - has nearly fully reopened its economy and seen its number of new coronavirus cases crash to almost zero, with just over 60% of the population having received at least one shot. Israel may be close to herd immunity to Covid Herd immunity happens when enough of a population has protection against an infection that it stops being able to spread - and even people who don\'t themselves have immunity are indirectly protected. For Covid the estimated threshold for herd immunity is at least 65%-70% of people having protection against infection, although Mr Biden\'s chief medical adviser Dr Anthony Fauci has increased his estimate to 90% and the World Health Organization (WHO) has said the level is not known. </string>
    <string name="news_b">Medical experts have yet again stressed upon the need to maintain Covid-19 appropriate behaviour even after one has received the first shot of vaccine. This for the simple reason that one is not immune against the virus till both the doses have been taken. And even after both the doses are taken, it would take certain time before immunity can kick in. Hence, if one isn’t careful then one could catch the virus even after a vaccine dose has been administered. India Today TV approached medical experts to get information on the issue as the Mumbai is undertaking simultaneous Phase One and Phase Two immunisation programme and is soon going to start with the registration for Phase Three drive. Doctor Rahul Pandit, Director-Critical Care, Fortis Hospital Mumbai says that antibodies develop within 15-20 days after the first dose which are inadequate to give protection and that it is after 15 days of the second dose when the antibodies effectively kick in. “One could be infected immediately after taking the 1st dose, could be a suspect patient, could have an active infection during the vaccination. Antibodies will give border protection only 15 days after the second dose, hence, coronavirus appropriate behaviour has to be maintained at all points.” he said. Recently, in Maharashtra, more than a dozen such Covid-19 positive cases came to light wherein the healthcare staff had already been administered the first vaccine dose. Doctor Lancelot Pinto, Consultant Pulmonologist, PD Hinduja Hospital and MRC says that positive cases even after the vaccine dose aren’t surprising or unexpected. He said, “One would expect the protection offered by the vaccine to take at least 2 weeks to manifest, and in the period before this, one can expect the risk of getting infected to be similar to that in the community. Even after 2 weeks, we know that the vaccine isn’t foolproof with a single dose.” On being asked about the issue of some healthcare workers getting infected after the first dose, he emphasises that the time when they got infected post-vaccination, the absolute percentage of healthcare workers who got infected and the severity of these infections would be important parameters to note. He adds, “There is evidence to suggest that one does not get severe disease post-vaccination, and if that is indeed the case, this would be very reassuring.” Doctor Pinto says that one shouldn’t be under the impression that the fear of the virus is behind us and we can let the birds down. </string>
    <string name="news_c">West Bengal chief minister Mamata Banerjee has announced that local train services shall be suspended in the state from Thursday onwards to combat the worsening coronavirus disease (Covid-19) pandemic situation. Meanwhile, metro rail and government-run transport services in West Bengal shall operate with 50% occupancy from Thursday, the chief minister announced. Click here for more details on the fresh Covid-19 curbs imposed in West Bengal on Wednesday. West Bengal on Tuesday reported its highest single-day deaths of 107 Covid-19 patients, which took the states death toll to 11,744, the health department had said in a bulletin. Meanwhile, a record number of new coronavirus disease cases were also registered, as the bulletin showed a single-day spike of 17,639 cases. West Bengals total Covid-19 infection tally currently stands at 8,98,533. The West Bengal chief minister also announced lockdown-like measures across the state to tackle the recent surge in Covid-19 cases, encountered in the second wave of the coronavirus disease. Shopping complexes, markets, gyms, cinema halls, and beauty parlours have been closed, while all manner of social and political gatherings have been prohibited. </string>

    <!-- Headings -->
    <string name="head_1">Biden aims to expand vaccines for adults and children</string>
    <string name="head_2">Just got my first shot, helping the world to be a safer place</string>
    <string name="head_3">Local trains to be suspended in Bengal from tomorrow in view of covid-19</string>


</resources>